Guide to the Sir John Orde Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Admiralty Papers, 1791-1824; Series IV; 0.63; (2 boxes)
  - Copy of a Correspondence, Partly Private, Between the Rt. Hon. Earl St. Vincent, etc., and Rear-Admiral Sir J. Orde, Bt., 1798 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Reports of Cases Argued and Determined in the High Court of Admiralty, 1798-1801 (Box 16, Folder 195-198)
  - Rules and Regulations of the Royal Naval Annuitant Society, 1824 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Series of Original Papers on that Great National Subject, the Improvement of the Art of Ship-Building, 1791 (Box 17, Folder 200)